blogtack.com 2014-02-08

# Privacy Policy | BlogTack.com

  * Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for this website.   
Information   
Respective owners deserve copyright of contents and information available on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collects information from user and other sources available at several different sections on our website. If any contact commenced with the reference of this site, there is no responsibility from the site owner. And we never give assurance of any kind of dealing.   
Registration and Inquiries   
In order to use some portions of this site, a user must complete the registration form. During registration a user need to give their contact information, such as name, email address. This information is used to contact the user about the interest on our site for which they have expressed.   
Cookies our site   
Cookie is a piece of script to stored data on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We never use a cookie to link to any personally identifiable information while user on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.   
Google Ads   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy. ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)   
Log Files   
We use IP addresses to analyze visitor's tendency, movement, and site performance and gather information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to any personal information.   
Links   
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users or visitors to read the privacy statements of any website before visit.   
Special Offers   
We may send all new members a welcoming email. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter.   
Site and Service Updates   
We may also send the user site and service announcement updates, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email.   
Correction/Updating Personal Information:   
If a user no longer desires to keep his / her information with this website please inform us to remove. If company information or personal information or content changes please inform us to correct. We will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that personal data provided to us.

### **[Search Engine Optimize](http://www.ampartech.com/index.php?option=com_content&view=article&id=54&Itemid=61)**

Search Engine Optimize (SEO) service provider for international clients as we achieved significant seo results by using the best seo techniques. The company has over 5 years of experience as an seo agency. Our seo techniques are tested and proven to be the best one for SEO campaign in the industry.   
For details and **[SEO package price](http://www.ampartech.com/index.php?option=com_content&view=article&id=54&Itemid=61)** click here 

### **[VoIP A2Z CLI and Non-CLI wholesale routes](http://www.bdphone.biz/index.php/routes)**

Stable and reliable A2Z wholesale route provider for Bangladesh, India, Pakistan, Nepal and other common countries for CLI and Non-CLI. If you are new or experienced voip businessman you can start 100% secure voip business with us. We are providing committed support and stable ports with lowest prices.   
Most of our routes ACDs from 7 min to 9 min.   
And ASR from 30% to 50%.   
We have also Singapore, Malaysia, Sri lanka, Egypt and other Asian countries routes.   
Contact us: bdphone11@yahoo.com, or bdphoneroute@gmail.com , skype: bdphoneroute   
For more details visit: [http://www.bdphone.biz](http://www.bdphone.biz/)

### **[Mobile Dialer, Java Tunnel, Pc2Phone](http://www.bdphone.biz/index.php/mobile-dialer)**

we provide Mobile Dialer, PC2Phone, Java Tunnel for Oman and UAE on Monthly Rent. 

\- itel Mobile dialer (200cc) monthly rent $300   
\- gPlex Mobile dialer (50cc) Monthly rent $165   
\- mTel Mobile Dialer (75cc) Monthly rent $ 80   
\- pc2phone for blocked country $20 per month   
\- Java Tunnel for Oman / UAE will be charged $20 dollar per month.   
For more details visit: [http://www.bdphone.biz](http://www.bdphone.biz/)
